iproduction.com 2010-12-01

# Privacy Statement

iProduction takes a firm position on privacy. We take your concerns seriously and want make sure they are clearly stated as they apply to your site visit.

iProduction will not use any personal information gathered: including email address, name, address, company name and phone number and sell it to any outside company. The information gathered is used to contact you concerning our products.

This privacy statement is subject to change. Users may view the privacy statement, including any revisions, by clicking on the "Privacy Statement" link at the bottom of any page of this website. If the changes represent a material departure from our current statement or materially affect users' rights and obligations, if feasible, the changes will be posted on this page 30 days in advance of their effective date.

## Passive Data Collection and Use

Like most Web sites, iproduction.com also collects and logs information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to you, such as your IP address, the name and location of your Internet Service Provider, the type and version of your browser, the length of time that you stay on iproduction.com, search queries, your click-stream data, the location that referred you to iproduction.com and the average number of pages viewed. If you visit another Web site prior to browsing iproduction.com, that Web site might place personally identifiable information within a URL, which may be logged by us. Your IP address is the identifier assigned to your particular computer when you access the Internet. Depending on how you connect to the Internet, your IP address may always be the same, or it may change each time you access the Internet. Note that logging your IP address does not in and of itself provide us with your name, e-mail address or home or work address. We use this log information for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes and may also use it to gather general demographic information about you such as your general location and your Internet Service Provider.

## Use of Personally Identifiable Information

Personally Identifiable Information may be accessed by iProduction personnel. We endeavor to keep your Personally Identifiable Information inaccessible to other users of iproduction.com.

We reserve the right to disclose Personally Identifiable Information when deemed necessary or appropriate to comply with the law, respond to claims, protect our computer systems and customers, ensure the integrity and operation of our business and systems, or protect the rights, property or safety of iproduction.com. We will not disclose your Personally Identifiable Information without your advance permission except as explained in this privacy statement or as explained at the time the information was collected.

## E-mail

iProduction does not rent, sell, barter or give away its user or member lists or its users' or members' names, e-mail addresses or mailing addresses for use by advertisers and other third parties for the purpose of solicitations, unless the user has previously given his or her consent at the time of general registration or registration for a specific service. If a user granted permission to receive solicitations (referred to as e-newsletter list) at the time of registration but subsequently wishes to opt out from receiving such solicitations, the user may opt out in their newsletter from receiving e-mail sent on behalf of Iproduction.com.

Our HTML-encoded e-mail messages include graphic files, which we use to gather information about e-mails sent to our members. When such a message is opened in an HTML-capable e-mail program, the recipient's computer accesses our server to retrieve the graphic file, and allows us to record and store the date and time, the recipient's e-mail address, and other standard logging information.

## General

In the event of the sale or merger of iProduction, ownership of the user registration information described in this Privacy Statement will be transferred to the acquiring or successor company.

iProduction endorses and abides by the privacy principles approved by the Interactive Services Association and the Direct Marketing Association. If you have any questions or comments about our policies, we may be reached at:

Office: iProduction, 1080 West County Road E, St. Paul, MN 55126

Effective Date: September 19, 2008
